<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soccer on Blake Aerni&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>http://blakeaerni.github.io/tags/soccer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soccer on Blake Aerni&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blakeaerni.github.io/tags/soccer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What color is London in the Premier League era?</title>
      <link>http://blakeaerni.github.io/2021/04/19/what-color-is-london-in-the-premier-league-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blakeaerni.github.io/2021/04/19/what-color-is-london-in-the-premier-league-era/</guid>
      <description>If you know almost anything about English football, you know that clubs that play in the same city have deep hatred for each other. The rivalries in London are a perfect example of that. The fans of these clubs love to make the claim that “London is (insert color of club)” when their club is having success. While the color of London seems to change every month or even every week in the eyes of the fans, I want to take a look at what color London would be if we looked at the entire Premier League era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much did no fans affect the 2020 MLS season?</title>
      <link>http://blakeaerni.github.io/2021/03/30/how-much-did-no-fans-affect-the-2020-mls-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blakeaerni.github.io/2021/03/30/how-much-did-no-fans-affect-the-2020-mls-season/</guid>
      <description>Soccer fans around the world know how much the crowd can get in the head of an opposing player, put a team off their game or just be supportive to the home team for 90 minutes. As far as we can remember this has been the case, but in 2020 our reality changed.
The 2020 MLS season played the majority of its games without fans, and even when fans were in attendance, they were few and far between.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
